When I saw Hetch earlier, I got a little excited.
さっきのヘッチ見てたらさ、俺もうちょっと興奮しちゃってさ
...
Sorry, just a little more...
ご めん、もうちょっと...
I'm not wearing any pants, but they're getting a little big...
パンツ履いてないんだけど、ちょっと大きくなっちゃってて...
I'm so excited...
興奮しちゃってさ...
If I could make you feel good too...
俺も気持ちよくしてもらえたら...
Is it okay?
いいかな?
Okay.
いいよ
I licked it from the tip
ちくりから舐めてちゃった
...
Try sitting on the blood while licking it.
舐 めながら、血の腰をかけてみて
...
Licking my balls...
玉 舐めてる...
In your mouth, no...
口にさ、やだじゃん...
So, just a little...
で、ちょっとさ...
I won't disappear, so I'll talk to you.
おさまに消えなくてさ、話しちゃうよ
...
Ah, I see...
あ、 そうか...
sweet...
甘い...
Was it sweet?
甘かった?
oh yeah...
そうそう...
delicious?
美味しい?
It was delicious...
美味しかった...